(We All Need a Day Like Today)
- Nice to see you, everyone. - My gosh.
Woo Il. Lee Jung. It's been a while, you two.
- Gosh, long time no see. - Hello.
- Long time no see. - Long time no see.
- It's nice to see you. - Where have you been?
- I wonder what brings him here. - Wait, Woo Il.
How did you end up getting so tanned?
I was abroad for two weeks.
I went to Southeast Asia.
I went to Indonesia and the Philippines.
We talked about you all the time.
- Really? - Yes.
- You should join us. - We missed you.
- You got us hooked. - Right.
I'm sure he came to see Lee Jung today.
- Right. - Yes.
- He's a fan of her show. - Right.
I really wanted to go to her concert.
- How about the one in November? - In November?
- Yes. - Sure.
You must go no matter what.
- Did you pass the driving test? - What happened with that?
Right, what happened?
(Lee Jung failed the driving test.)
I'll try...
- to pass the test this year. - Okay.
I'll give you all a ride.
- I think I'm good. - You...
You can give Woo Il a ride.
(She'll give her true fan, Woo Il, a ride.)
(Retouch)
"Retouch."
(The sound of brushstrokes fills Kian84's studio.)
It's his studio.
I could have done this in one go.
(Kian84 is working on something.)
(Amazed)
That's huge.
What's the size number for this?
The size number is 120.
Darn it.
But why do you look so unhappy?
Darn it. This is so annoying.
Why are you cursing?
I've been trying to work on my art.
But trying to work on my art...
while starring on TV shows and running...
might have weakened my concentration.
Or I just might be struggling to channel myself into my work.
- But it's true that I'm struggling. - Really?
(His passion has been driving him for the past few years.)
(He managed to win the Grand Award...)
(while pulling off a busy schedule.)
- Right, you're so busy. - Congratulations.
(He successfully completed the New York City Marathon.)
(In no time, running has been an important part of his life.)
I ran about 240km just in September.
- For 1 month? - Yes. I ran about 230 to 240km.
- He ran a lot. - He ran more distance than a car.
That's true.
Then you ran at least 8km every day.
Running improves your health, but makes you age fast.
- It makes you age? - Yes.
- It ages you? - It quickens...
- the aging process. - He does seem older.
Isn't it because you're running way too much?
- Maybe it's excessive. - Yes, cut down on running.
- Here's the thing. - You can cut down on running.
I'm not a good runner.
Because I want to improve, I end up running a lot.
Good runners run a lot because they want to stay that way.
That's how we're all turning into Sean.
- Let's say you keep running... - If you stop running...
- and you improve. - Right.
Then the distance you used to run...
- won't satisfy you. - Right.
- Yes. - You'll have to run a little more.
When runners take a break, their endurance declines a bit.
I work on my art at least three days out of the week.
Do you have time for that?
Well, I like some of my paintings,
not all of them.
I feel like I'm in a slump.
(Out of frustration, he tries to change it around.)
(Does it look good?)
Darn.
(He goes back to brushing.)
You know what I noticed about him?
He has such high standards for his work.
The standards keep going up.
I drew cartoons for a long time.
But I've been painting only for 3 to 4 years.
So I'm still painting like a novice.
(Let me think.)
That looks pretty good.
- You're blurring the lines. - Yes.
I guess you painters are on the same page.
That technique is called sfukato.
- What? What was that? - It's to blur the lines.
- Sfukato... - Gosh, this is so annoying.
(Gosh, this is so annoying.)
- I guess you're right. - Yes. Of course.
When you look at Mona Lisa,
- the lines are blurred. - You're bringing that up?
We use the technique to blur the lines.
- It's to soften the lines. - Yes, to soften them.
- You can click as a fellow painter. - Of course. It's profound.
- I knew it. - You should learn from me.
- He's the best painter. - I'll stop painting now.
What?
You gave high praise for his work in Illo.
(Gosh, your drawing has improved a lot.)
(He recently spoke highly of Moosquiat's work.)
- I was just saying that. - Really?
- Was it an empty compliment? - It was good. But...
You're annoyed that...
- he's compared to you, right? - This is annoying.
I wasn't treated like this when I drew webtoons.
Let yourself be...
- motivated like this. - Okay, Hyun Moo.
(Kian84 keeps reapplying the paint.)
(Groaning)
Gosh, this is exhausting.
This isn't working out.
(Complaining)
Darn it.
What don't you like about it?
The thing is, acrylic paints don't mix well.
They dry up fast.
(Come on, just blend already.)
(Thud)
Darn it. The chair...
- Why are you so angry? - Why do you sound so stressed?
- So... - The chair did nothing wrong.
when I go home after painting,
- I'm in a foul mood. - Well...
I'm so happy when I paint.
I used to giggle when I drew cartoons.
I used to giggle...
- while working alone. - Right.
- But art is different. - When something doesn't go right,
nothing goes right.
That's so true.
Lee Jung, do you also curse when you can't execute some moves?
- I do that a lot. - Really?
That defines...
- if it's your hobby or career. - Right.
- We get serious if it's our career. - It's not my career.
- Right. That's true. - Of course.
- Kian84 has a goal. - It's fun when it's just a hobby.
I always want to do better than what I'm capable of.
- I guess you're not satisfied. - No.
(It's not easy to satisfy himself.)
(He grabs a working chair.)
(Then he focuses on brushing once again.)
(Groaning)
Come on, I can't seem to get this right.
(He dislikes his painting even more than usual.)
Darn it.
(Darn it, I'll stop here.)
- That looks great. - It's great.
I couldn't execute it the way I envisioned it.
Nothing ever works that way.
(Grunting)
(He grabs another canvas.)
(He tosses the painting to the floor.)
(He was inspired by Rembrandt.)
- I'm working hard on this. - Wasn't it from earlier this year?
I repainted it.
Is this how artists think?
(Kian84 brings out something else.)
(Opening)
(He applies the gesso before painting.)
- That's gesso? - Gesso.
What are you doing, Hee Min?
You're doing a hideous job with your painting.
(Glancing up)
(What should I do?)
(Startled)
(Shocked)
- Did you paint that over? - Why?
- That was great. Why? - Why did you do that?
- What a pity. - Gosh, that's such a pity.
I have a question. Why did you paint that over?
- I should reuse the canvas. - Right, it'd be a waste.
- Because it'd be a waste? - Not to waste the canvas?
Partially, yes.
When I don't like it, I just paint over it.
- Painters do that? - Yes.
Here's what I thought. So you didn't like that.
You could've kept it as it was.
You could have started with a new canvas.
Once you get another inspiration, you can work on that again.
All the time and effort would go to waste, otherwise.
No. To do that, I was too frustrated with that.
- It was that bad? - I see.
I have a question then.
How do you work on your art, Moosquiat?
- Let's say I'm not satisfied. - Yes.
I give it away as it is.
"That's how you look."
- You leave it as incomplete? - Even if it's not what you wanted?
If it's not...
"I hate it." Then I give it away.
"Here you go."
My gosh. Come on.
How many months have I been working on this? It's all wet now.
Hee Min.
I didn't like that either.
So I painted that over with gesso.
It's been one and a half years since my last exhibit.
I didn't like any of them.
So you couldn't have another exhibit.
I tried to paint clearly like animated cartoons.
Then I tried utilizing gemstones.
- They were beautiful. - I also tried doing oil paintings.
Then I came back to working with acrylic paints.
I'm not a good painter or anything.
So I should be happy with whatever I have.
But in my own way, I try my best to produce a good painting.
Because there's no deadline,
I keep changing my approaches.
I try out a method. If I don't like it, I start over.
So that's why I'm not so happy...
when I paint these days. I'm quite stressed out.
Right. You used to laugh a lot when you did cartoons.
(He also taught people what he was good at.)
(Painter84 used to depict romance.)
- Gosh, he looks so young. - Yes, he does look young in this.
(Working with paints is still unfamiliar,)
(but he's been practicing it for the joy of it.)
Right. You had so much fun back then.
I forgot about that.
Yes.
- What a pity. - Right.
(He spreads gesso over it with pursed lips.)
Did it dry up?
(He poured his heart into painting these waves.)
(He spreads the gesso on top of them without hesitation.)
I guess it's equivalent to potters breaking his works.
What could I do, though?
I can't display a painting I don't like at my exhibit.
My gosh.
I get what he's going through, but what a bummer.
(His work of 7 months goes back to a blank canvas.)
Seven months?
- Do you see another white canvas? - Yes.
I worked on that for four months. But I painted that over too.
- What? This... - You did? My goodness.
My gosh. No!
Darn!
No!
(He accidentally makes a big mistake.)
- Oh, no. What's he going to do? - My gosh.
Oh, how tiresome that is.
Darn!
(Spilling over)
(Speechless)
Why do all the bad things happen...
- in one day? - Right.
There's a day like that. Seriously.
This is driving me crazy. Come on.
(Nothing is going my way today.)
(Disgruntled)
(He tries to save whatever he can.)
Oh, no. The carpet is ruined.
Come on.
What's wrong with me?
- You're most upset with yourself. - Right.
- You'd be so annoyed. - You can't blame anyone else.
- Right. - Come on.
What a way to pile it on.
(He removes the remaining gesso on the canvas.)
(The carpet, his hands, and clothes are all stained.)
(What a royal mess.)
You sweated a lot.
(He changes into his regular clothes from his work clothes.)
(Grabbing)
- He's leaving. - Right. When it's not working,
- you must do something else. - Right, you should stop.
Ae Ong. Meow.
- We rarely get to see Ae Ong. - Right.
I'm leaving.
(Coy)
(Kian84 leaves after working for hours.)
Hello.
(Kian84 is heading somewhere in a taxi.)
Where is he going?
Are you suddenly done with your day?
Or to refresh?
Thank you.
How will he refresh himself?
- I really hope it's not running. - Stop running.
Judging by his outfit, he's not going to run.
- What? Is he going on a trip? - What? He's going out of Seoul.
You can buy art supplies at the Express Bus Terminal.
- Right. - My gosh.
It's funny how he keeps thinking like a painter.
It's been ages since I last visited.
(As Moomoo predicted, it's an art supply store.)
This place is huge.
I didn't know there was a store like that.
It's been a while.
They still sell the plaster busts.
- Of course. - Yes.
Arias.
Arias is the only one that comes in medium.
- They have names? - Of course.
- She's probably a princess. - I see.
One of the things I've worked hardest on in my life...
was drawing plaster busts.
- I did that for my college exam. - Look how young he looks.
That's how I got into college.
That was the exam.
That was a long time ago.
- To get into an art school, - That was the exam?
everyone practices that.
It's been over 20 years since I stopped working...
to help students get into college.
But I always drew one every 3 to 4 years.
I loved sketching plaster busts.
Pencil drawing is...
the most basic form of art to observe and depict objects.
Every athlete does weights...
whatever sport they play. It's equivalent to that.
To improve my basic skills, I wanted to draw one...
- after a long while. - You're going back to the basics.
- So I bought a bust of Arias. - Yes.
And I love her smile. When you look at her lips,
they curl up like this.
I like her lips.
The smirking princess.
Not a lot of people buy this, right?
- Actually, people buy... - Really?
Arias more than you think.
I guess people still do pencil sketching.
People buy this more than you think.
Thank you, sir.
Do you have a small easel?
- Which one? An easel? - Something like this.
I should get one of that.
- Thank you, sir. - Sure.
- Have fun. Thank you. - Okay.
You look like an art student.
- Is that so? - He used to go to an art school.
(Like an art student, he knows what to do.)
I want a 6B pencil.
Could you give me a sheet holder for the easel pads?
- My gosh. - Oh, my.
Yes. People look artsy with the holder.
- He does look like an art student. - Do you have Kent paper?
Kent paper? This way, please.
(He takes a look at them.)
All done.
Thank you.
(He places the paper into the holder.)
It had been a while since I held that.
Have a good day.
(He swiftly buys everything he needs.)
Aren't you registered in our system?
I did spend a lot of money here.
I'm a VIP customer there.
Of course, you are.
- I'm not? - No.
You should sign up. They give you a discount.
Do students draw plaster busts to get into art high schools?
They don't do that for college, right?
- Right. - Right?
Have a good day.
(The former art instructor knows everything.)
(He's getting into a taxi again?)
Hello.
(Struggling)
- That's big indeed. - That's huge.
It's medium-sized, so it's pretty big.
It's like two people are getting in.
She's sitting next to him?
(It's taking some time to reach the next destination.)
- Hanam? - How far are you going?
You can stop over there, sir.
- It's here, right? - Yes.
- What's in Hanam? - You...
Did he move to Hanam without telling us again?
- He moved to Hanam? - No.
(Looking around)
Is this the entrance? I've never been here before.
Where is this place?
Is this it?
(Ringing)
- Kian84. - Hey, it's been a while.
- What? - It's been a while.
- My goodness. - Hey, it's been a while.
- It's Chung Jae. My gosh. - It's been a while.
Mr. Starlight. I haven't heard this song in a while.
- It's Chung Jae. My gosh. - Yes.
I was stressed out from painting.
So I naturally missed Chung Jae.
There's the bright glow in his eyes.
When you're stressed, you must look at beautiful things.
Only his clips get a slow-motion effect.
He looks cool even when playing catch.
I don't end up with a solution.
But he listens to my problems.
He sympathizes with me.
When was that?
- That was a long time ago. - My gosh.
But he hasn't aged at all.
- My goodness. That's me. - He looks exactly the same.
That's Na Rae.
(Their first meeting was full of excitement.)
(Look at Na Rae!)
- Her face is red. - Hello.
(Yes, I remember that day.)
(Walking down memory lane)
He looks exactly the same.
He hasn't aged at all. His skin is still milky white.
He's indeed handsome.
What's the age difference between you...
and Chung Jae?
Do you want to guess?
- Well... - Gosh.
- What a lame question. - Be honest.
- About seven years? - What?
This is so annoying.
Stop running now!
I do agree that I look much older.
- How many years are you apart? - Only two years.
- No! Hold on. - My gosh.
- I'm so sorry! Oh, no. - How could you tease him like that?
- No. I meant... - My gosh. No.
Why are we shaking hands?
Are you trying to make it go away?
- Lee Jung. - Get your hand away!
Lee Jung. He just looks younger than his age.
- Right. How can he look that young? - Right?
I was actually going to say five years.
- I wanted to be funny. - Yes.
You're so mean.
- I was trying to be funny. - Yes.
- I believe you. - I mean it. I'm serious.
He's the perfect art student people dream of.
He's the perfect example of that.
- Right. He is. - That's right.
You know what I read online?
Someone asked, "Will I see people like Chung Jae at an art college?"
"There are guys from Kian1 to Kian84."
(There are guys from Kian1 to Kian84.)
- That comment hurt my feelings. - From Kian1?
Kian1, Kian2, Kian3, Kian4...
- Kian75... - Like "Mickey 17?"
- Yes. - "Mickey 17."
I was feeling good today.
This ruined my mood now.
So which numbered Kian is the best?
Of course, it's Kian84. Obviously.
- But... - I think Kian84 is the best one.
He's the best.
Gosh, this is the place?
- It's nice with the high ceiling. - Gosh, no.
(Happy to see him)
How long has it been?
My goodness.
We met at my exhibit last year. Right?
Yes.
It's been one and a half years since then.
It's been that long?
Yes.
Why do you look so tanned?
I've been running a lot these days.
- You got slim and tanned. - Yes.
- Did he get facial treatments? - He doesn't get stuff like that.
He doesn't even apply lotion.
It looks like he barely goes out in the sun.
You know what? If he runs three marathons,
he'll get tanned and lose his sparkle.
What have you been up to?
- I recently did a group exhibit. - Okay.
The pile over there is from the group exhibit.
I'm sorry I couldn't attend your exhibit.
It was a group exhibit.
- It was iffy to invite you. - Okay.
But it still turned out well.
Anything else?
I've been working since then.
- I've been painting. - Have you been painting?
Hey, give me a tour of your studio.
I need you to explain what's what.
- His studio has gotten bigger. - Yes.
(He's been holding exhibits regularly as an active artist.)
- He's focusing only on his art. - Right.
He's known as the handsome art major.
I'm at Chung Jae's studio now.
He moved his studio about three years ago.
I've been busy with work,
so it took me a long time to visit his studio.
(This is nice.)
And on this side,
I have the kiln in the back.
(His studio is also equipped with a kiln.)
- He does all kinds of art. - For pottery?
- That's after the bisque firing. - Okay.
- That's how it looks. - You changed the shape.
I've been trying out different shapes.
- You're over there. At the top. - My gosh.
That looks so eerie. Why does it look so eerie?
- It looks so eerie. - My gosh.
(Kian84, sleeping in the art studio)
- Hold on. - What's that?
A long time ago when I visited his studio,
we created my bust together.
- What was that called? - That's the bust.
The things at the Mausoleum of Qin Shi Huang in China...
- The Terracotta Army? - Yes.
- But... - In the Terracotta Army,
there's a soldier with that face.
Was that a meaningful project?
- That's... - Creating a bust together?
That was a long time ago.
One time, he was working on sculptures.
- He did a great job. - I asked him to make one for me.
- That's so fascinating. - It looks just like him.
It looks just like him.
(Rummaging through)
- So how is it going for you? - What's that?
How's your art coming along?
I wouldn't say it's going well.
- Okay. - But I'm grateful...
that I can continue.
Really?
He's so cool.
He says the coolest things too.
- He's cool. - But that's a fact.
Good-looking people are not as ill-tempered.
- Of course. That's because... - They grew up with love.
- everyone is nice to them. - Yes.
I doubt they had to face any injustice.
That's why when I'm stressed out, I go to Chung Jae.
When I see him, it softens my anger.
Yes. That's right.
- You used to do that? - Yes.
Your visit must've stressed him out.
Chung Jae? Gosh, I'm not that ugly.
- I look pretty good too. - Come on, don't be so mean.
(Kian84 shyly glances at Chung Jae.)
Chung Jae, here. I've got a present for you.
It's my first time visiting your studio.
You can open it.
I rarely do stuff like this.
- What's that? - What is it?
This brings good luck.
It's a pollack.
- My gosh. - Yes, that's cute.
That was so thoughtful.
- The real fish might've smelled. - Yes.
- That's cute. - That's better.
- Right. This is nice. - Yes.
- Luck. - Bring me a lot of luck.
It jingles too.
A lot of people give that out as a present these days.
- It's a big trend. - Yes.
I brought the plaster bust today,
so we could draw together.
- Draw the plaster bust? - Yes.
- That's why you brought Arias? - I brought Arias.
It's almost been two centuries since I last saw it.
(He comes to face her after a long time.)
- She's expensive these days. - How much?
This used to be less than 30 dollars, right?
It's 70 dollars now.
But the price didn't go up that much considering the inflation rate.
You carried this from the supply store?
I did.
Hey, let's draw her together.
- I'm drawing her too? - Yes,
you should since I'll be drawing her.
You need to brush up on your basic skills too.
It's been so long since I last did one.
- I'm not sure if I can do it well. - It's been 6 to 7 years for me too.
But It's fun to do it at times.
Okay then.
He accepted it.
I wanted to draw with him.
He did cast drawing in the past, after all.
When I ask Chung Jae to do something with me,
he obliges without a complaint.
He's like that.
(That's why I'm always thankful.)
Thank you for doing this with me today, Chung Jae.
Doing this so suddenly...
makes me feel like an instructor at an academy.
We worked together at an academy back in the day.
I bet it brings back memories.
We did similar things together when we were younger,
so the activity put me at ease.
There are 4B and 6B pencils.
(They sharpen the pencils as they think about the past.)
(Plopping down)
(The two artists sit across from each other.)
It's like a youth drama.
Chung Jae looks like a character in a movie.
- It's slow motion. - What?
You don't look bad.
(Let's do a good job.)
(Laughing)
Why is this so funny?
(Doing the basic drawing again makes him embarrassed.)
Hey, it's nice.
It has been so long since I did this.
- Don't you need an extender? - What's an extender?
You put it at the end of the pencil so that it becomes longer.
You use it for short pencils.
(Rummaging)
(He heats up a pen.)
- All right. - What's up with the lighter?
- What's that for? - People did that back in the day.
People used pens and markers as an extender.
- The old markers. - Yes.
Since I didn't have an extender, I made one with what I had.
Why do you put an extender on the pencil?
It increases the radius of rotation.
- The length. - You can cover more area at once.
The radius increases.
It has been a while, so the extender looks strange.
Why did it come out so lousy?
This pencil is short.
Come on.
Why is the BGM going, "Starlight is falling?"
- It did fall on his face. - His face?
(It has been a while since he held a pencil for drawing.)
Kian84 is sitting in a dark spot.
That's right. He's sitting in a dark spot.
Everyone, please focus on the drawing.
That's what you should focus on.
I don't even remember how I did it in the past.
Really?
How did I draw it?
(How did I draw it?)
(Glancing over)
It was fun to do it again after a while.
I bet it brought back memories.
It's the healthy kind of therapeutic time.
It seems like you always miss the time you worked...
- at the art academy. - Me?
Why am I always hung up on the past?
Everyone is like that.
Your desire to do the cast drawing tells me...
that you can't forget the past.
Back then...
(You have a point.)
You have a point. It's...
one of the things I worked hard on in my life.
It hurts my shoulders and arms more than I remember.
(Despite the hardships,)
(the two artists draw as they did in the past.)
(Decalcomania)
We look similar.
I'll need to visit the studio twice more to complete the drawing.
(He tries to go back to the time when he was a passionate rookie.)
It's hard.
Chung Jae, let's order some food.
Okay. What should we order?
Chinese food. Can you order it?
Of course. What would you like?
- Stir-fried jjajangmyeon. - Stir-fried jjajangmyeon?
I'll order tangsuyuk as well.
Okay.
- I ordered it. - Okay.
- What? Did Chung Jae pay? - Yes, Chung Jae paid.
Before we eat...
(Let's focus.)
(Rustling)
(Arias begins to take shape.)
(Focused)
- It's nice to see you so focused. - Yes.
- You look relaxed. - That's right.
- His facial expression changed... - Yes.
from the time when he was at home.
He looks so happy.
(Winking)
You're right.
You aren't swearing.
You look more cheerful and joyous than you did...
- when you drew earlier. - He isn't stressed out now.
- It was fun. - Right.
Kian84, you should've closed one eye.
- That's right. - Why is my tongue coming out?
(He goes back to his rookie days and focuses on the drawing.)
- You're good. - It's fun.
That's his talent.
- How fascinating. - It looks incredible.
It's really fascinating.
(Time passes quickly like the bygone days.)
How did I do this in four hours?
- It's really hard. - Right?
The college entrance exam...
(The two artists are exhausted as they haven't drawn in a while.)
was strange.
At first, Chung Jae played around.
- But he became absorbed soon. - You're right.
When you made your artworks, you felt the pain of creation.
- You put gesso over your work. - Yes.
Was your heart at ease back then?
- It was fun. - You found it fun.
I enjoyed it. It was like playing a game.
(As if they're playing a game, they enjoy drawing.)
That means you aren't fed up with arts.
That's right.
- It's fun because it isn't work. - I guess so.
In the industry Lee Jung and I are in,
working on the choreography of the title song is...
so pressuring that it drives me crazy.
- It's work. - That's right.
- That's right. - One song must show everything.
But when we work on other tracks of the album...
- We're much more at ease. - There's no pressure whatsoever...
- That's right. - when we practice.
- It's the same. - So,
- the artists and I have fun. - That's right.
We get excited and work freely.
- That's right. - Yes.
(They draw in a relaxed way without any pressure.)
I'm hungry. I hope the food arrives soon.
(Staring)
- What? It's here. - Really?
When did the food get here?
(They were so focused that they didn't know it was here.)
I didn't know that it was here.
(They have a meal after awakening the drawing senses.)
Did you order regular jjajangmyeon?
I ordered the regular one.
I'm exhausted.
These days, I can't even draw for five hours a day.
I keep doing different things,
so my ability to concentrate on my artwork...
keeps suffering.
Back in the day when I drew webtoons,
I could draw for 12 hours a day.
You were young then.
Until 3 or 4 years ago,
I could draw...
like a machine.
You're incredible.
When it comes to fine arts,
I've only done it for 3 to 4 years.
At times, I don't even know what I'm doing.
(I see.)
I don't know if I should continue on with it.
I just try to work hard since I've begun.
(After unloading his worries,)
(he finally takes a bite.)
(Impressed)
It's tasty.
(Na Rae's mouth waters.)
It looks tasty.
(He eats hurriedly with jjajang on his mouth.)
This year,
I got so many offers to be on shows.
Had I accepted all the offers,
I would've been as busy as Hyun Moo.
Had I accepted all the offers, I would've had no time to draw.
So, I draw in my spare time.
Making artworks...
(Making artworks requires a lot of time.)
requires a lot of time.
(Sighing)
Time is limited,
but there are so many things I want to do.
That's right.
But if I'm not careful, I won't succeed in anything.
You went there to unload the worries in your heart.
That's right.
Also, people say that running...
makes your day lively by filling your body with energy...
and helps you with work as a result.
But I get so exhausted after running.
I lose energy, so I can't work afterward.
(I can't work afterward.)
- Really? - Yes.
Maybe it's a bad exercise for you.
I lose energy.
When you run...
- So many people recommend it to me. - Right.
All of them say, "Since you work so much,"
"you should run and increase your stamina."
- No. - No?
- You'll die. - You'll lose your stamina.
I'll lose my stamina?
This lifestyle suits us.
- Really? - Each person has the set amount...
- of energy per day. - Energy.
- That's right. - There's the set amount.
One time, I ran in the morning with my dancer friend...
and it ruined my entire day.
- Really? - Yes.
I'm at the important crossroads.
I ran in the morning with Sean once, right?
- Yes. - It ruined my entire day.
It was too early.
I could see that.
It depends on the person.
Some people gain energy...
- That's right. - while others get tired.
Really?
- It makes no sense. - This is driving me crazy.
What am I supposed to do? Should I run or not?
I lose energy, so I can't work afterward.
(The morning run makes him even more exhausted.)
I thought running was your way of relieving stress.
It does relieve stress.
But...
- it makes me lose time. - I see.
That's the situation I'm in.
It's understandable.
(Nodding)
If the Han River has...
a wise man named Sean,
Hanam has a wise man named Chung Jae.
That's what I think.
- He's a wise man. That's right. - A different kind of a wise man.
When you think about it,
when you look at him closely,
he smiles like Buddha.
(His smile is as kind as Buddha's.)
His T-zone is fair.
Poisonous thoughts well up inside me at times.
But they go away when I meet him.
- Chung Jae does detox. - That's right.
- He has that effect on you. - That's right.
(Impressed)
You should meet him often.
(He clears the bowl.)
Last year, I counted my artworks after the exhibition.
I had made fewer than 20 artworks in a year and a half.
Aren't 20 artworks a lot?
When I made webtoons,
- I made over 100 cuts in a week - What?
- I worked on a computer, - Webtoons are different.
but I thought, "Even if I work on canvases,"
"I'll easily make four artworks in a month."
But... I actually worked fast in the beginning.
I worked fast and produced many artworks.
But as time goes on, my productivity decreases.
Maybe you shouldn't compare your current self...
to the past self.
- That's right. - That's right.
You made a good point.
I sang "View" ten years ago.
It's a beautiful memory. It was a moment of my youth.
But I can't compare my current self to that version of me...
because it makes me fester inside.
- That's right. - I had to stop comparing the two.
- It makes you fester inside. - Yes.
You need to come up with the new self...
that suits your current age and situation.
- You made a good point. - That's right.
KEY is absolutely right.
Back when you made webtoons diligently,
- you were only on this show. - That's right.
- You looked happy when you drew. - That's right.
The situation has changed.
When you reach a certain age,
you have so many responsibilities...
even when you don't look for more work.
So many.
From the bills...
to the family members, friends,
and juniors as well as their issues...
You get more responsibilities, and it's a natural course of events.
- That's what I think. - That's right.
You should set a different standard.
(He had many pent-up worries.)
I should let go of greed.
- That's a good idea. - It's because of greed.
(Nodding)
(Meeting up with Chung Jae makes him open up his heart.)
It was a nice meal.
- This restaurant makes tasty food. - They're good.
- Thank you for the food. - What?
Why would you say that when you paid?
I'm still thankful for the food.
It must be nice to have a junior who buys you food.
(Thank you. I'll take out the trash.)
It's 6pm already.
(Now that we've had a meal, shall we resume drawing?)
(The two of them get back to work without resting.)
(They become absorbed in drawing without any thoughts.)
(They become true to the basics of the art.)
(They draw without rest in the same spots.)
We drew for three hours and a half.
(They remain seated for over three hours.)
Hey, it's hard!
Do you think you got the basic drawing skills back?
No!
It's just hard.
(Even though it's hard, he keeps moving his pencil.)
- It's very exhausting. - I'm exhausted.
(My entire body aches.)
(Staggering)
(Shall I stop here?)
It looks cool.
(How does Kian84's drawing look after 3 and a half hours of work?)
(Let's see.)
Why is it so light?
- The cast is light in color. - Right?
The drawing should be light.
Right.
(Now comes Chung Jae's drawing.)
It's nice.
(My goodness)
He still has the basic skills.
- Kian84's drawing is nice. - It's cool.
They drew the same cast,
- but the drawings are so different. - Their styles are different.
- Their styles are different. - It's fun to see that.
- They're really good. - Right.
- I'll take this. - Okay.
I want to get back to it when I have time.
I hope you didn't get more stressed out at the studio.
I didn't.
I hadn't done it in years,
so I'm proud that I could do it somehow.
I guess you forget the techniques if you don't use them.
(In a container, he puts the drawing he made after a long hiatus.)
Will you keep on working?
No. Because of this...
(He can't work anymore.)
I have no energy.
- I'll need to go home. - Really?
- Are you exhausted? - I'm exhausted.
You should finish your work.
(He averts his eyes.)
(He plops down again after gathering his belongings.)
(Yawning)
All right.
- Well done, Kian84. - Okay.
- Good luck with your work. - Okay.
- He's sending Kian84 away. - He wants Kian84 to leave.
- He's pushing Kian84's back. - Seriously.
"You should go, Kian84."
- "You should go home." - "You should go home."
- You should leave then. - That's right.
You should go, "All right," and leave the studio.
I don't want to go home when I meet Chung Jae.
You must love him a lot.
- "You must love him a lot." - Being with him puts me at ease.
- In every age group... - There are such friends.
- That's right. - That's right.
- You want to spend time with them. - That's right.
(My goodness)
(Gosh)
Please massage my neck.
Harder.
(It feels nice.)
(Slapping)
"All right. Let's go."
Do you know what he'll do next if Kian84 still refuses to leave?
He'll begin to turn off the lights.
- That's right. - Then he'll leave with Kian84.
He'll begin to vacuum the floor.
- That's right. - "I turned off the AC."
You should turn off the AC first.
"Let's close the door."
Why did you finish it so quickly?
Come to think of it, my hands are covered in pencil lead.
Okay.
(I'll put away the cast statue!)
Look at that. He must have an appointment afterward.
He's putting everything away.
I'll get going.
Okay.
(Chuckling)
I'll get going. Stay inside.
- Bye, Kian84. - Okay.
Bye.
Kian84 is disappointed about...
- going home. - He's disappointed.
- Having beer would've been nice. - That's right.
(He puts disappointment aside and hits the streets again.)
- Hello. - Welcome.
He's disappointed. There's disappointment on his face.
It was good to see him again after a long while.
That's right.
You should meet up with Chimchakman.
My goodness.
Hello.
(Grunting)
- Is this a pansori singer? - What's up?
Which slippers should I wear? Can I wear any pair?
- Hold on. - Wear any pair.
- Did you actually go to him? - He's Chimchakman!
Chimchakman!
His real name is Lee Byung Gun.
His former name was Lee Mal Nyeon...
and his current name is Chimchakman.
(He was Kian84's roommate in the past.)
Here's what I think.
(He's Kian84's close friend who used to draw webtoons too.)
Now, he doesn't draw at all.
His job completely changed.
When I tell him my worries,
he gives me answers from a perspective...
I've never thought about.
His way of listening to my worries...
is different from Chung Jae's way.
Chung Jae is...
I go to the temple from time to time when I feel stressed out.
Just as if I visited the temple,
I visited Chung Jae.
As for Chimchakman,
I visited him as if I went to hang out at a comic book cafe.
I went to hang out with him.
(A place he goes to as if it's a comic book cafe)
Gosh.
- Aren't you busy? - Nice socks.
Aren't you busy?
I'm always busy.
Are you done with work?
Yes. I'm done with work.
- What's this? - This?
- A plaster figure? - I drew this today.
- Today? Why? - Yes.
I just felt like it.
Do you want to try drawing it as well?
I don't know how to.
You drew these to enter college before.
I'm awful at drawing them.
- Is this his office? - It's his office.
The place where he films for his content?
- It's fascinating, isn't it? - It's fascinating.
Right!
- I saw this place often. - Right.
So this is where he films for his content.
(Just like a comic book cafe,)
(the office is filled with cute items.)
- How much was this? - This?
They're a lot more expensive now.
They weren't even 30 dollars back then,
but they're around 70 dollars now.
- Really? - Yes.
- It looks nice, doesn't it? - Have a seat.
Why draw this all of a sudden?
- What? - Why draw this all of a sudden?
I draw these from time to time.
- Regularly? - Yes.
Didn't you just get this?
Did you draw it at an art school?
No. Chung Jae's studio is in Hanam.
I went there to draw it.
Their conversation consists of only short answers.
Do you want to draw with me?
No. I don't know how to.
It's just drawing how it looks.
I don't know how to draw these things.
The tone feels different from when talking with Chung Jae.
That's how it is.
Tones differ between friends.
- Right. - I didn't realize that at all.
It feels completely different.
"What?" It feels like this with him.
- You guys go back and forth. - You're right.
I heard you don't draw these days.
I don't draw now.
- You... - I heard you retired from drawing.
Right.
It was because...
people kept expecting things from me.
Who? No one expects things from you.
When I appear on a show or something like that,
they ask me if there's something I have drawn.
They ask if I can draw on the spot.
I get it.
That was why...
I was forced to announce my retirement from drawing.
People might think...
you're someone like Mr. Huh Young Man.
Why announce your retirement from drawing?
I would keep being asked to draw...
if I didn't do that.
Oh, I'll get you some coffee.
(I'll get you some coffee.)
Gosh.
Are your shows doing well?
- My shows? - Yes.
I'm just doing what I can.
- The coffee is in highball glasses. - Right.
You seem to be doing well.
What do you mean I'm doing well?
I'm not doing much.
I've been drawing these days.
I've been struggling though.
He feels like an elder at a real estate agency.
- Right. It feels comfortable. - A trendy real estate agency.
You've been drawing a lot.
There was a big pile of drawings when I visited you the other time.
I did draw a lot,
but around five of them...
seemed worthless.
- Five of them seemed worthless? - They weren't good enough.
- Out of how many? - I drew around 20.
Five of them seemed worthless.
I saw the ones that I completed...
- You didn't like them? - and I didn't like them.
It feels harder the more I try to draw.
Are you feeling stressed out these days...
because you aren't feeling satisfied from your drawing?
These days? Yes.
I don't know what I'm trying to do.
Being on shows and drawing...
were two of the main things I did.
Running...
suddenly became a part of my life.
- Right. - So...
I can't seem to focus on one thing.
I understand.
You can't do 20 things that you like all at once.
- Right. - Right.
- You have to be less ambitious. - Right.
I can't seem to focus on one thing.
Get it out of your life then.
- Get what out? - Running.
He's so straightforward.
- Get rid of running. - I can't get rid of running.
- Why not? - It's my main profession right now.
Then be on fewer shows.
- What? - Be on fewer shows.
- Be on fewer shows? - Yes.
What do you usually do during the week?
- Me? I run. - Yes.
- You run. - I run some more.
Gosh.
I draw.
I curse.
Right.
(I see.)
Do you enjoy running?
Yes. I enjoy running.
I'll be running around 35km tomorrow as well.
How is running 35km possible?
- That's over a half marathon. - Right?
How would you draw after running 35km?
- That won't be possible. - No.
You won't have the strength to pick up your brush.
I'm a water deer these days. I go crazy.
- It's all settled then. - What?
It's all settled if you enjoy it.
Is that so?
Has anything changed in your studio?
When was the last time you came?
I think it has been around a year.
You briefly visited the fourth floor, right?
You're still doing well after moving here.
(Walking around)
I like this type of drawing.
Back then,
I didn't think highly of it. I like it now.
- He didn't think highly of it? - Right.
I thought you were awful at drawing in the past.
But it looks impressive now.
"Impressive?"
We started with drawing comics, but we don't draw anymore.
Right.
You still draw these days though.
I thought I shouldn't be giving up on that.
It's still...
- Why does that matter? - something I started with.
What kind of angle is this?
It feels like an independent film.
In movies like "Decision to Leave,"
they stand like that when sharing delicate emotions.
(Scene 5: Sharing delicate emotions)
We didn't want to look at each other's faces for a long time.
- What? - But if I think about it,
I don't think I've looked into my friend's face when talking.
- It's weird to do that. - My male friends.
It will feel weird to do that with true friends.
We just need to be aware of where we are.
I thought I shouldn't be giving up on that.
It's still...
- Why does that matter? - something I started with.
"I started with drawing and I have the roots of drawing."
"I must not give up on drawing."
- There's no need to think that way. - Well,
that was something I got complimented for throughout my life.
You still get complimented for other things.
- But... - You're a great runner.
No. I won't get any compliments for my running.
I'm not that good.
- You don't need those compliments. - Others run over 80km.
- What? - Must you get complimented?
I still should get complimented for what I do.
I got really impressed by him while watching his shows.
"Who cares if you're not so good?" He seems to have this mindset.
Right. He was always like that.
This is what I think.
The acts that you do are impressive.
- You do extraordinary acts. - Right.
You should make them into a form of art...
and do performance art.
You tried sitting and drawing all day long,
but you didn't get what you wanted, right?
You like moving around, don't you?
Apply paint to your feet and run!
- That's what art is. - Right.
Mix up the things that you like.
Why use the brush and your feet separately?
Use them together.
- But... - You're great with your feet.
That would make me seem like too much of an attention seeker.
- No. - People would think that way.
- I think it's a good idea. - What?
It's a good idea.
He always comes up with a solution.
When I tell him I don't want to age, he tells me to become a cyborg.
- That's a clear solution. - Right.
- He's a great friend. - That's great.
He's full of ideas as he's a cartoonist.
- It's best to speak nonsense. - Right.
- It helps relieve stress. - Right.
What else is there?
- There's the fourth floor. - Right.
(Let's go up.)
I don't think it will be a bad idea to do that.
It's just the same. It's nice.
This was when you were on YouTube.
Right.
Your drawing is here as well.
- Where? Right. - You drew this.
- What is that? - Gosh.
(Kian84's masterpiece in Chimchakman's office?)
Your drawing is here as well.
- Where? Right. - You drew this.
(Kian84 is doing a tour around Chimchakman's office.)
It's still here.
- What is that? - Gosh.
- Right. - "Chimchakman's Future."
It was drawn in 2024. It has been a year.
This one.
All of my employees left except for one.
- Really? - There's one left in the office.
The two who were in the office...
are working on their own now.
- They became independent. - That's great.
It's like they've finished their training.
So that's what they do.
Like how chefs become independent and run their own restaurants.
Right.
I visited them, and they were working hard on their own.
It would be great when they visit you after becoming successful.
I would love it for them to be successful.
- Definitely. - Right.
- I'm rooting for them. - Right.
You must have a lot to work on.
- Well... - Why do you only have one employee?
When my employees help me out,
- I fix all of their work. - Right.
That takes up more time.
You were always like that.
- I just... - You did all the work.
don't know how to work as a team with others.
I'm not like one of those global masters.
I heard those people had 200 to 300 assistants.
I'm not someone who is at that level.
The number of assistants isn't what's important.
Right.
If you want someone to work just the way you want them to work,
you must invest a lot of time to that person.
- He sounds so mature. - Right.
But you don't tend to do that.
It takes a lot more time to match each other.
That is why you need to invest a lot of time...
- to the people you work with. - Right.
You need to reduce the time of your running sessions.
- It's the same solution. - It's the same solution.
- It always ends there. - "Run less."
Run less...
and get into sync with the one who draws with you.
- Right. - You have to do that...
to be able to work with 1 or 2 people.
Right.
It's the same process for 200 to 300 people.
You were like that when you worked on webtoons.
Right.
You ended up doing everything.
Your assistant drew a part for you,
but you sat there and fixed everything.
But back then...
You just moved around to do all of the drawing.
- He moved around a lot. - Gosh.
- He's right. - He sounds so cool-headed.
There was a lot more to work with when working with the others.
I just needed to add the details for their webtoon work.
But for drawing, it's different.
It's harder...
with drawing.
It's hard to find the perfect person.
It isn't easy to do that.
(A serious conversation in slippers)
I'm not here to share my struggles with you.
Just apply paint to your feet.
Do that.
You can run for a long time.
- What? - You can run for a long time.
- I'm not that great of a runner. - It's a different spot to run.
- I'm not a great runner. - You can run on top of paper.
On top of paper?
Whether it be 10km or 20km long.
I think it will seem like a work of art.
- Thank you for giving me advice. - You seemed frustrated.
- What? - You seemed frustrated.
I always get frustrated.
He's a great person to talk with.
- He's very calm. - Right.
- Should we play Starcraft? - What?
(A video game battle after a while)
- This is the best thing to do. - This is fun.
It seems so comfortable.
(Totally immersed)
(Doing his best)
(Laughing)
This is fun.
You're finally laughing.
- You're finally laughing. - This is so much fun.
Those simple things are the best.
It's fun to do the things you did in the past.
Right.
There's a different therapeutic vibe at this place...
- from Chung Jae's place. - Right.
(Smiling)
Gosh, it's been a while since I played.
This is what I think.
When I first started working on webtoons,
I felt excited after waking up in the morning.
"I can express these things today."
It felt exhausting after working on them for a long time.
I think it's the same with the drawing I'm working on now.
I don't feel satisfied with my work...
and it feels exhausting.
I'm going through that process.
But whenever I feel that way,
I can talk to my fellow artists...
and it clears up my thoughts.
This is my way of overcoming those struggles.
Why are you here already?
- Hold on! - Hee Min!
Gosh.
(We can't see each other often like before,)
(but we always feel comfortable whenever we meet.)
You're good.
- I can beat you in the next one. - Should we play another round?
- What? - Should we play another round?
(Okay! I've Made up My Mind!)
- What? - What could it be about?
(Fast asleep)
Everything is white.
That must be a great place to sleep in.
You have a nice couch.
I've been sleeping on the couch for three months now.
(Walking)
Gosh.
- How cute. - How cute.
(Getting up)
Gosh.
(He heads straight into his dressing room.)
He has so many clothes.
I'm sure he doesn't wear all of them.
- Are you asking for some clothes? - It seems he is.
What are you getting on to?
I'm the first one on the list to get CODE KUNST's clothes.
(Securing his place)
He must be leaving right away without washing up.
(He gets changed to head outside while being half asleep.)
(He picks up his phone that is still ringing.)
(He leaves the house 10 minutes after waking up.)
Where could he be going?
(Walking)
He must be out for a walk.
(He follows the trail.)
The weather is great.
I should keep checking the time.
What's going on?
What? I don't have much time left!
I have to hurry!
- Emergency! - What's going on?
(He moves quickly as he seems to be short on time.)
Is it an opening rush?
He isn't someone who would do opening rushes.
- Hello. - Welcome.
- Welcome. - All right.
- You're here. - Right.
Shall I start shopping?
I see.
Is someone visiting?
It seems too early for that.
What was I going to buy?
(Picking up)
(Let's see.)
Gosh.
(He made a shopping list on his phone.)
Eggs.
There's a list for the things that are needed.
Right.
Hello?
(I don't know what to do.)
(He called Jang Woo to ask about the things to buy...)
(as he felt lost.)
What else was there?
How nice is that?
The protein drink.
(It heads straight into the basket.)
(He gets the things on the list without hesitation.)
It won't fit in the basket.
Will this be enough?
(Packed)
- There are that many things? - Is he having a snack party?
Okay. There we go.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- See you. - I'll come again.
Okay. Goodbye.
I should take around five minutes until I get back home.
I have enough time. It's 11:57am.
Why is he constantly checking the time when he just went shopping?
(He keeps checking the time while heading back home.)
Siru.
(I'm back, Siru.)
Let's go.
(He places the things he bought in the kitchen.)
I should get changed first.
(He returns after getting changed into comfortable clothes.)
All right.
- I'm done with that. - What's going on?
I'm done with that and that.
What is that?
It's my schedule for the day.
It's just for that exact day.
While being under more control,
I thought that I would spend the day without making mistakes.
That was why I gave it a try.
You wanted to try living like a planner?
(You wanted to try living like a planner?)
I was planning to get my album done within the year.
An album takes around two years to make.
It takes around two years on average for an album.
But it's already my third year to work on the album.
This was when I started working on the album.
It was when Kwang Kyu visited.
(Around 2 years ago)
(Happy to see him)
I stopped at around 80 to 90 percent with each song.
I kept writing new songs at that point.
I ended up writing about 160 songs like that.
I thought that I wasn't going to finish the album within the year.
When I was on "Show Me the Money,"
I wrote 12 songs in 3 months.
- Right. - Right.
There was a deadline every week.
- Right. - There's this saying.
"The best source of inspiration is the deadline."
Right.
We had to come up with comedy skits for the very next day.
We did it with ease.
I did more than 50 percent of the work on deadline day.
I came with all of the storyline on that day.
I set deadlines with the schedule.
Actually,
I considered myself to be a great planless person.
I was someone at the peak...
of being planless.
(While eating a banana,)
(he threw the table tennis ball.)
(While organizing his clothes,)
(he lied on top of them.)
He was spontaneous.
I was like an animal in the zoo.
I did everything...
that caught my eye.
(Planless person at the peak)
He seemed to be free.
Ki Bum is the only real planner among all of us.
- Right. - Out of us.
- I'm right in the middle. - Right.
- You go back and forth. - Right.
I'm more of a planner.
- Who? - What?
- You? - Really?
You come here when it's hot.
All of that is planned.
- Really? - Gosh.
- Do you control the weather? - It's all planned.
- I consider everything. - You know when it'll be hot?
Of course.
I'm a hardcore planner when I travel.
I type everything out...
- and print 2 to 3 pages. - Really?
- For real? - I give them out.
- Oh, my. - To people you travel with?
When I travel...
Let's say the plane leaves at 1pm.
Then I'd pack at 10am that day.
What? The very day?
- I do that too. - Right?
I pack on the day I travel.
Because I studied abroad for many years,
I can pack quickly and leave.
- You're way below me. - Why?
I buy clothes at my destination.
(Why prepare in advance?)
- That's... - I travel with one outfit.
- Me too. - I don't bring anything.
- Toothbrush, toothpaste, clothes. - That's right.
- You're so romantic. - I just leave.
- That'd drive me crazy. - That's right.
- I'd just dress sloppily. - Socks.
I just need to cover myself.
(Spontaneity versus planning, a conflict of opinions)
Everything will be planned today.
Just everything.
Today, I'll become a planner.
(He becomes PLAN KUNST to complete his album.)
I'm so disappointed in you.
(You betrayer)
(11am, wake up)
That's why you keep timing everything.
(11am to 12pm, grocery shopping)
What else?
(Bacon, eggs, milk, banana, bread, fruits, loaf of bread)
(12pm to 12:30pm, walk home)
You're very planned.
That's done.
Gosh, this isn't hard.
(He checks the time again.)
(It's 12:19pm.)
(12pm to 12:30pm, walk home)
In the spare time...
(Thinking)
I should do things like this.
(Using his spare time to feed Siru and Panda)
I'm going to rest until 12:30pm.
I'd do the next task in advance if I have spare time.
Oh, really?
If I can't do the next task in advance, I can't help it,
but if I can, I would too.
Come here.
(Lying down)
(A relaxing time with Siru and Panda)
They're cute.
Gosh.
How adorable.
They're so dog-like.
(Jump)
(Getting up right away at the sound of the alarm)
- Oh, you set an alarm... - Okay.
- for every task you have. - That's right.
The cool guy's next task is...
(Let's see.)
The cool guy's next task.
Organizing the fridge.
Organizing the fridge?
- You could've done that in advance. - I know.
- That could've been done. - That's doable.
- But a first-time planner... - That's a very tight schedule.
shouldn't move up the task.
- In case you ruin the rest? - You were worried it'd be ruined.
(Opening the fridge, following his planner)
I got a new fridge.
My brother went to the US to study,
so he gave me the fridge he had.
He really eats little.
Yes. Now it feels like a real home.
There's nothing much, though.
Call me if you need to clean out the food.
You want to take that little of food I have?
The types of food that I can save time...
and quickly be done with.
I wanted to make that.
(He planned to organize the fridge to make it more time efficient.)
(It's 12:30pm.)
The drinks...
"So they can be taken out right away."
I drink them most often, so I'll put it on the topmost shelf.
Mom's side dishes.
(Following through his rules)
I'll put them here.
(Beeping)
That's what spontaneous people hear the most.
The beep.
That's right. I hear that a lot too.
(With the familiar sound, he quickly puts away his grocery.)
Olives.
Do I keep the bread in the freezer?
Since this is also scheduled, you need to move quickly.
Stir-fried kimchi, garlic, dried laver.
How should I put away eggs?
What?
- Oh, dear. - Oh, no. Time's up.
- What time is it? - It keeps ringing.
I feel so anxious.
(12:30pm to 1pm, return home and organize the fridge)
Wait.
(It's 1pm now. The time's up for his task.)
(The clock ticks away quickly.)
(But he's not done organizing his fridge.)
Close the doors! Just please close the doors.
Today, I'll become a planner.
(Will PLAN KUNST be on pause?)
- No, don't scratch your nose, - Is he contemplating?
and close the doors.
- I'm almost done, though. - Yes, just carry on.
You can keep going.
What's the next task?
Oh, lunch? Okay, then.
I should eat quickly, then.
- He's making use of the time. - Forty minutes is too long.
He's taking time from the next one.
I'll finish lunch in 25 minutes.
You cut down on mealtime.
(It's 1:01pm.)
(He'll keep organizing the fridge for the remaining 14 minutes.)
(Picking up)
Organizing the fridge isn't an easy task.
- It's hard. - It's hard.
(As he's late, he quickly moves.)
(So he wouldn't be late for the plan he fixed,)
(he keeps checking the time.)
(Pouring out)
You need to move boldly at a time like this.
You need to do household chores on a day like that.
That's right.
Oh, yes.
You're good.
- It's neat, indeed. - And you can take it out...
right away.
You're right.
This is crazy. The fridge looks cool.
(Satisfied)
(12:30pm to 1pm, return home and organize the fridge)
(1:15pm to 1:40pm, lunch)
Now, then...
(He prepares lunch right away.)
What is this?
(Checking the time)
Wait. I have to eat within ten minutes.
(I should make it quickly and eat it.)
But it must take time to make lunch.
(Preparing sausages that can be cooked fast...)
(and fried eggs that's easy to cook)
All done.
It'll be perfect if I eat this as well.
(With instant rice,)
(he's done preparing lunch.)
- That's American-style breakfast. - Wait.
Bread and rice? What kind of combination is that?
(It's 1:33pm.)
(He has only 7 minutes to finish his lunch.)
(He eats bread without hesitation.)
Having bread and rice at the same time feels new to me.
It really is unusual.
Is that so?
(Nutrient consumption for survival)
(Taking a glance)
How many minutes do I have?
(It's 1:37pm.)
He has three minutes now.
- Gosh, you don't have time. - What will he do?
(Munching)
He's forcing down food because there's no soup.
He really eats to survive.
But I really enjoyed it.
(It's 1:39pm.)
- He's having a banana too. - Gosh, it must be so dry.
(He even has a dessert with 1 minute left.)
I feel like the alarm is going to drive me crazy.
- Yes. I'm so stressed. - That's right.
Even a planner finds it hard.
(Done with lunch)
(I'm full.)
I'm so full.
(He does the dishes as soon as he's done.)
Gosh, I forgot the resting time.
(1pm to 1:40pm, lunch)
(1:40pm to 1:50pm, rest)
You had ten minutes to rest?
I added time to rest.
You'll need to do the dishes instead of resting.
(PLAN KUNST even planned a time to rest.)
Four minutes?
That kind of helped.
- Really? - Really?
Otherwise, I'd have taken five hours to organize the fridge.
It's true I've never seen you...
- move that fast. - That's right.
(He speeds up to meet the time.)
(I need to finish this in 4 minutes.)
(I'm going to finish the dishes within the resting time.)
(1:40pm to 1:50pm, rest)
(Fortunately, he finished the dishes within time.)
That's done.
- I'm done with lunch. - I think this is better.
It looks like a diligent life.
Remember how I did that before?
- Locking up my phone? - I remember.
(I need to detox.)
(Don't come out!)
(He tried to take a break from screen time with determination.)
(8 hours and 28 minutes)
(He used his phone for more than eight hours.)
But now, I only use my phone 3 to 4 hours a day.
- Really? - Gosh.
You reduced it a lot.
Just like that. I'm a really spontaneous person.
I thought I needed to improve my daily routines.
Within 30 minutes.
(He moves on to the next task.)
(1:50pm to 2:30pm, clean Mabaem's house)
All right, Mabaem.
(A corner of his room is filled with things.)
(A room for vivariums)
It's gotten bigger.
- Oh, as in lizard. - Oh, lizard.
(1:50pm to 2:30pm, clean Mabaem's house)
(His love for lizards began with Dae Ho.)
A lizard.
(He decorated his first vivarium.)
It's going up!
Where? Here?
(His vivariums have been upgraded.)
This is a carefully planned vivarium.
- That's so cool. - He's doing it in earnest.
(The temperature and humidity are carefully taken care of.)
- They were the ones you had. - Yes, Cono and Coho.
(Cono and Coho he had before and a baby lizard)
(Cute)
Goodness, how cute!
- This is a new guy. - Oh, it's new?
They're the same species, but they're male and female.
They made me think that I raised them well...
because they spawned a lot.
So there are three eggs in the incubator.
I'm maintaining the eggs myself.
- I'm trying my best. - They have a good relationship.
So you have five in total.
There are 5 lizards and 3 eggs, if you count the eggs.
It's mystical.
I think he surpassed Dae Ho.
Dae Ho spread this in his living room.
That's right.
What's worse is that that's the same kind of sand.
He's become a human lizard.
How did he spread this in the living room?
Dae Ho, come out for a second.
(Dae Ho ended up becoming a lizard himself.)
- They're so cute. - They're bigger guys.
Dae Ho, I need to clean that part. Can you move?
I still can't believe he used this on himself.
I kept getting reminded of that scene.
- Dae Ho must love it. - Yes.
(I should spread this for my lizards instead.)
Mabaem.
- How adorable. - Look at its eyes.
(He evenly spreads sand with love.)
Mabaem, can you move?
(Jumping)
- Don't get mad. - It's so cute.
(Satisfied)
(He grabs the lower case after he's done cleaning the upper one.)
Gosh, I should clean this.
Mabaem. Oh, okay. I'm sorry.
You always get mad at me during the day.
(Even though Mabaem is mad, he cleans the house with love.)
- Look at you. - Oh, my.
- It's so cute. - I know. It's so adorable.
You'd be mesmerized when you touch it.
(Spraying)
(Providing refreshing water)
It's so cute!
- Gosh, it's so cute. - It keeps coming to you.
- It keeps coming to your side. - It must be in a good mood.
(While he's focused on his task...)
Go back in now.
(Pulling)
- Gosh, look at that. - Look. A thermometer.
That's what a pork belly restaurant uses.
All right.
You must study a lot to maintain those.
- You must study. - It's so cute.
He's really serious about this.
I've always liked raising things since I was young.
You need to study a lot to raise lizards.
That's right.
(Wiping every single leaf)
- So much effort. - He's putting in so much effort.
If you don't clean them,
they create toxic gases.
Go back in now.
Why wouldn't you go in?
(Crawling around as they are excited by the new sand)
(Feeling proud)
(Satisfied with a cleaner house)
- It's so cute! - Look at you.
And then...
(Opening)
These eggs... It's about time they hatched.
Are you hatching them?
I didn't expect this either.
They must have a really good relationship.
September 14.
These are viable eggs for sure.
It's about time they hatched.
He lives alone there, so how come that place has such good energy?
I'm not sure about this one, though.
(I hope they hatch soon.)
(Knocking)
- What? - What?
(Who is it?)
Yes? Okay.
(Someone is visiting him when he doesn't have much time?)
Gosh.
What is it?
What's that?
- Is it a tree? - A plant must've been delivered.
That wasn't part of my plan.
(Here's an unexpected variable.)
This had to come now?
(The tree had to be delivered now, of all times?)
(I still have more to clean.)
- This has to come now? - His tasks are getting backed up.
What do you do in a case like this?
For instance? What would you do, KEY or Na Rae?
- If this happens, - Yes.
I'd acknowledge the tree,
then I'd go back to the previous task and wrap it up.
Then I'd squeeze that in somewhere in the plan.
He's getting to it right away.
- He does it right away. - We get it done right away.
That's the tree I ordered 2 or 3 days ago.
I was really flustered...
because the plan will go off track.
"But I'm a planner."
"This shouldn't happen." That's what I thought.
Let's put this here for now.
Wait. This looks strange.
Gosh, he shouldn't be fixated on that.
- What is that? - It's over if he becomes fixated.
I didn't like where it was.
It's not that aesthetically pleasing.
Wait a minute. I'm pressed for time.
- No, you have to clean. - Why doesn't it suit the room?
(It's less than 5 minutes before the cleaning time is over.)
Over here?
(He quickly moves the pot.)
Gosh, it looks somewhat messy.
If so...
- He's fixated on that. - Oh, no.
(He's replacing the pot when he must be cleaning the lizards' houses.)
- Gosh. - What do we do?
I should get back to my original task.
That's right. Goodness.
(He quickly gets back to the lizard house cleaning.)
(Rushing)
No!
- Gosh, that's bad. - Wait a minute.
- Gosh, I'm so stressed. - I thought it was my phone...
- that was ringing. - I'm stressed now.
It's 2pm.
What was I supposed to do now?
(Rushing)
He's going back to the fridge to check?
Still, you did your best.
Oh, cleaning the cats' blankets.
Cleaning the cats' blankets?
Cats?
(I need to quickly clean the cats' blanket.)
(He quickly wraps up cleaning the lizards' house for now.)
I'm being rushed now.
(I'm so busy.)
I need to clean this room too.
(Tasks have piled up in no time.)
(2:30pm to 3pm, clean the cats' blanket and litter boxes)
(The clock is ticking.)
- You should wrap that up first. - That's right.
First of all,
I'll clean the blankets quickly.
I'll save ten minutes from there...
and use that time to clean up this room.
(That sounds okay.)
Okay.
(Get to it right away.)
Then...
(It's 2:34pm.)
- That song is driving me crazy. - That song... Seriously.
(2:30pm to 3pm, clean the cats' blanket and litter boxes)
What? How do I undo this?
- The cat tower? - Yes.
What about the blankets?
So while I was cleaning the blankets,
I was reminded of that.
Right. Well done.
(He's given up his plan.)
This must be waterproof.
- This wasn't part of his plan. - Yes.
This song is driving me crazy.
I'll be reminded of it when I go back home.
- You should throw them. - That's good.
(Throwing)
- Throw them. - Did you watch this in advance?
(Fascinated)
Spontaneous people just throw them.
It feels like you watched it in advance.
(Throwing)
- He'll reposition them? - Reposition furniture.
Let's try turning it.
(I must reposition the sofa, if nothing else.)
It was my first time moving that sofa since I moved.
- I see. - I see.
So that's how it looks.
Hey!
(Crawling in)
Why would you go in there? Hey, come out.
- Right, cats ought to... - How cute!
- You punk. - It looks like the cat...
from "Puss in Boots."
- Look at you. - It's like the cat from "Shrek."
- I know. From "Puss in Boots." - It's so cute.
You're the variable.
- Look at you. - How cute.
- It's so cute. How can you... - How cute.
- not take a photo of that? - Tell me about it.
Siru.
(In the end, he had to pause his plan again.)
You can spend 30 minutes like that.
I know.
I need to turn it.
(He comes to his senses again and repositions the sofa.)
(He brings a vacuum cleaner in the middle of repositioning.)
(He moves the sofa again.)
(Then he suddenly cleans his dressing room.)
Siru, come here.
(Now, he doesn't care if the alarm rings or not.)
It's ringing again. What is it this time?
(Forget the plan. It's all messed up.)
Gosh, that sound. Seriously...
- I'm so stressed. - I'm so stressed too.
The laundry is done.
- The blankets? - The blankets are done.
- Why are you laughing? - I got hit with reality a bit.
Oh, no.
Goodness.
(Laughing)
He's losing it.
(The alarm became his work song.)
The cat left.
(Everything is a mess.)
It's already 5:30pm?
- Why do you look so worn out? - Your eyes...
- The dark circles... - I...
- He lost weight. - I lost weight.
This is why it's dangerous to be a planner.
- What are you talking about? - What are you talking about?
It's nice to rest.
(But the house is a mess.)
Everything's brought out.
You're watching your own clip.
No, I'm not.
Is that a first birthday party?
He's doing doljabi.
Doljabi?
No.
(The alarm went off while watching his doljabi clip.)
(Getting up)
What's he doing now?
He's kicking everything around now.
I think your anger is building up.
You need to go see Chung Jae.
- Call me next time you see him. - Okay.
Your anger disappears when you meet him.
(Taking the planner he stuck on the fridge)
- He's leaving just like that? - That's right.
He leaves at exactly 6pm.
- Oh, to the studio. - Oh, to the studio.
This is important.
I thought I needed to finish working on the songs...
that were 70 to 80 percent done.
Actually, I spent the day like that because of this.
- Because you need to... - Of course.
- spend more time on your music. - To make good music...
(He heads to the studio on his bike.)
(Worn out)
- What's wrong with your face? - Are you sure you're okay?
- Why are your under-eyes so dark? - The reverse triangle zone...
stands out especially today.
You look so...
I did too much work that day.
(Laughing)
(Speeding on the bicycle path)
It was the evening rush hour. It was right at that time.
Because there's traffic.
I wondered how I could get there within 30 minutes.
I could only do that by bike, if not by teleportation.
Bicycles are the best there.
- It's way faster. - What is this?
(Do not ride bicycles here.)
- You have to push it. Right. - That's right.
- You have to push it on a bridge. - You have to push it on a bridge.
(I've been walking for quite some time.)
(I might be late at this rate.)
It takes exactly 30 minutes to get there, right?
Gosh, the alarm.
(The alarm goes off as soon as he reaches.)
(6pm to 6:30pm, going to the studio)
I'm here.
That's amazing.
I feel like he needs a nap now.
No, he should get an IV drip.
Really?
(Setting something up instead of an IV drip)
I should blend these two.
Gosh, what is that?
A coffee machine.
- Its design is really nice too. - Yes.
If I remove this...
(Coffee transfusion that will ease his fatigue)
(Satisfied)
(He heads straight to the studio after recharging his energy.)
(Let me see.)
Let's start working now.
- You should turn that off! - Darn it.
Just turn it off now.
(The alarm rang the whole day.)
- It's like a Japanese horror movie. - Exactly.
I look like an artist after a long time with dark circles.
(9:30pm, finish working on the song)
(He'll focus on work until 9:30pm.)
You'll start right away?
- Without resting? - I didn't want to go off schedule.
(Even though he's tired because he moved around all day...)
If I didn't get to work, all the things I did during the day...
would be pointless.
- True. - That's right.
You did all that so you could focus on work.
(His ultimate goal is to make nice songs.)
(Getting up at the sound of the doorbell)
It came so fast.
You delivered in?
(He ordered food before he started working.)
(Flopping)
You're not eating it?
If I eat it...
- You lose the flow. - Yes, I lose the flow.
If you started working, then you should continue.
(Stacking each note carefully)
Nice.
He's so cool.
It must've gone cold.
(Grabbing)
- What's that? Gosh! - What?
- What is that? - What's that?
Is that a skein or something?
(Even if he drops his food,)
(he doesn't miss the beat.)
He looks like a producer who lives a productive life.
You can multitask though.
(To me, even a spoon...)
(acts as a metronome.)
(Sparkling)
(He savors music instead of food.)
Goodness.
- That's him swallowing his food. - He's bobbing like this.
- Is that so? - He's swallowing noodles.
Because it's not good?
- It looks like his stomach is full. - His eyes and his head bobbing...
It's all done.
Did you complete a song that day?
I finished three that day.
You're a super Type J.
I started working on those songs half a year ago.
But I got to finish them only now.
(He finally finished the songs that were pending for half a year.)
I think it helped improve my concentration.
There were about ten chapters today,
You were really busy.
so I thought it was too much.
It felt like how I did when I first encountered multi-grain rice.
I know it's not delicious at all,
(Even planning)
but it's good for yourself.
If I divide my day into two chapters,
which will be working out and going to the studio,
that's be a big improvement for me.
I wrapped up the songs.
You must've felt proud of yourself.
I'm a perfect planner.
You did all those, in any case.
- I did all of them. - You did.
Have you been drawing up a plan after that?
I don't set time for anything.
I'd think, "I'll go to the studio in the evening."
- Right. - But I've changed it...
to going to the studio by 7pm.
- Or by 8pm. - It's not a rough plan anymore.
No. My plan got more detailed.
That's awesome.
But his house is a mess.
- You need to plan cleaning again. - That's right.
(I'm going to enjoy the three completed songs for now.)
- "A Plan Man." - "A Plan Man."
(Next story)
(Hyun Moo, can you beat me?)
(The history of Moo-Ku started with Sung Hwan's provocation.)
Let's run 100m in front of the MBC building.
(They had a barefoot race against each other.)
(But Hyun Moo easily beat him.)
(Let's have a proper field day.)
(Let's do it.)
(What about prizes?)
(I prepared them all.)
(Then I'll take MINHO.)
(The long-awaited...)
(The 1st Innocent Moo-Ku Fall Field Day)
(The field day has started.)
(They prepared the field day themselves.)
(Now that we're done preparing, let's have fun!)
(This is exciting!)
(Why isn't everyone coming?)
(A group of people in white appears from afar.)
They're dancing.
(We're here for the field day.)
(Why did you pick a day like this?)
What are they doing there?
(A bunch of beloved family members shows up.)
(Welcome)
(Kang Yong appeared with his secret weapon.)
(Splendid prizes that the CEO of MBC send himself)
(I must win them.)
(The first crew, Team Chunk)
(I'll beat them with my sheer strength.)
(I've been waiting for this day.)
(Heave-ho)
(Helpless)
(The chunk roars.)
What are you doing? Are you a woodpecker or something?
(The second crew, Team Weirdos)
(Immersed)
(They've become a lot closer,)
(and it makes them laugh.)
(The third crew, Team Go-getters)
(The main go-getter, MINHO)
(And Ji Hyeon is next to him?)
(Neck and neck)
(I'll fight with guts and grit.)
(Victory and defeat hang by a thread.)
(We are just as fearless.)
(Getting interesting)
(The go-getter finds it unfair.)
(MINHO, are you ticked off?)
(MINHO, are you hurt?)
(Filled with desire to win)
(Let's face off for real.)
(I can't let them take even a single point.)
(A strong determination to win)
(I can do this.)
(We don't stop.)
(But is this right?)
Let's fight with sincerity.
(It won't stop raining.)
(The match won't end either.)
Everyone's lips are blue.
- Please... - Lower.
(We might all die at this rate.)
Can we just end it?
(Never Ending Innocent Moo-Ku Field Day)